rayashop.com 2015-04-12

# Rayashop.com is an Online Shopping Website and Also is an online source for mobile phones, Laptops, electronics, LCD TVs, DVD players, computers, cameras, games and more. Research, compare and buy securely online.

**Privacy Policy:**

We will only use your personal information (name, e-mail, Phone number and address) in the way we specified when it was collected. We will not subsequently change the way your personal information is used without your consent. Some of the ways we may use your personal information include: 

  * • To provide the ability to create personal profile areas and view protected content. 
  * • To provide the ability to contact you.
  * • To provide customer feedback and support.
  * • To provide contests, sweepstakes or sending promotional e-mails. Personal information may be collected to administer those programs
  * • To conduct questionnaires and surveys in order to provide better products and services to our customers and end users. Your completion of any   
   questionnaires is voluntary.
  * • To support recruitment enquiries.
  * • To understand more about you, so we can personalize newsletters and websites to your preferences. For example, allow you the opportunity to request   
   specific information on products and services that may be of interest.
  * • To allow you to forward information to another individual such as a friend or co-worker. Raya does not store the personal information of the third party.  
   We collect the information for the sole purpose of sending a one-time email. If you choose to use our referral service to inform a colleague or friend,  
   we will only ask for a contact name and email address.
  * • To meet contract obligations.
  * • You will be able to unsubscribe anytime by clicking on the unsubscribe link at the bottom of all our email communications.

**Privacy policy of sent resumes:**

Raya will use your personal information for recruitment purposes, and if you are offered a job or become employed by Raya, for other employment-related purposes. By submitting your resume/C.V. information to Raya, you agree that we may use it for recruitment purposes (including transferring the data to other countries, transferring your information to other companies authorized to perform specific services for Raya, and/or other processing relevant to recruitment purposes).It will not be shared with others for non-recruitment purposes. Resumes/C.V.s should include information relevant to your employment history and education (degrees obtained, places worked, positions held, relevant awards, and so forth).Raya recommends that you do not disclose sensitive personal characteristics (e.g. gender, height, weight, religion, philosophical or political beliefs, and financial data) in your initial resume/C.V. or letters to Raya 

Copyright © 2012, Rayashop.com Owned and Managed by RAYA TRADE

Address: 26th July St., Touristic Zone, 6th of October, 12568 Egypt  
Tel: +(202) 3827 6000   
Fax: +(202) 3827 6001   
E-mail: webmaster@rayashop.com
